graygrids.com 2019-07-13

# Privacy Policy - GrayGrids

    Last Updated on - 24/05/18

We are very serious about user data privacy and value them in best possible way. All of our registered users informations ( Name, Email, & Address ) are secure to us. We are committed to take best care of there information and we are promised to our customers that we are never going to share there information with anyone.

 **The GDPR** (General Data Protection Regulation) is an EU-wide privacy and data protection law that gives individuals more control over their personal data. It places certain obligations on businesses that process information of individuals.

We embrace these changes, and have made a big change to our Privacy Policy, to comply with the transparency requirements under GDPR.

### Information That We Collect –

  *  **From Customers and Registered Users:**  
We intentionally, ask very minimal information from customers to make the conversion much easier and hassle-free. We collect customer name and email as personal details. We also collect temporary information about your system such as – browser, site usage statistics, IP address, and general location by your browser for security purpose. Billing and payment details are collected only when you make any purchase, which is submitted by you.

  *  **From Authors:**  
We collect name, store name, support email and payment details from author to send commissions and contact them for serious reasons such as – future follow up, author-customer conflicts and verification purpose.

  *  **Purpose of Collecting :**  
We don’t allow to make a purchase or get access to restricted contents anonymously, so we collect these to identify you as a user, provide future access to accounts to download your purchased products, to manage your products (if author), sending product updates, getting feedback and sending marketing materials. So, the ultimate goal is to provide access to your assets, identify authorized user and send product updates/follow up.

 **Who Can Access:**  
We do not share, rent or sell your data to third-party only GrayGrids has the access to your submitted data. You have full freedom to keep and update your personal details using your account settings and able to delete your data including account completely by sending an email to hello@graygrids.com.

 **How Long We Keep:**  
As long you have an account with us, we have your name and email address, if you unsubscribe and delete your account we won’t have access to your data.

 **How We Process:**  
If you make any purchase or register on our site, we will have your basic information via forms to identify (name and email) which are saved on our server located in the US. These data are used to identify as a registered user – to provide support, provide future access to your purchased products, to manage your products (if author), sending product updates, getting feedback and sending marketing materials.

 **Policy for Under 13 Children:**  
No one under age 13 years old can provide personal information on our websites and not able to make any purchase.

 **Links to External Websites:**  
We have so many resourceful blog posts – on the product reviews, tutorials, and other related resources. Some of them will redirect you to third-party websites. If you click on a third-party website link, you will leave our site and go to the site you clicked. We cannot control activities of third-party websites, we are not accepting responsibility for any use of your personal information by those parties.

 **Usage of Cookies:**  
We are using cookies (third-party services we use such as – Google Analytics, Facebook Pixel etc. using cookies behalf of us) to analyze user behavior, gather demographic info about our user base in general and other statistics. If you don’t like to cookies get placed on your browser, please disable cookies from your browser settings.

 **Data Protection:**  
We are very conscious about the data breach and protection. But, If in case any data breach occurs such as – alteration, unauthorized access, or loss of data. We will immediately notify you by email.

 **Your Control Over Your Data:**  
You have full freedom to keep and update your personal details using your account settings and able to delete or request a copy of your data by sending us an email to hello@graygrids.com.

 **Marketing Emails:**  
If you register on our site or subscribe our newsletter you are part of our community, we will send you newsletters/emails that will include product updates, latest releases, or discounts that we feel might be of interest to you. If you decide not to receive such email notifications you can easily opt-out using the unsubscribe button from email or send an email to hello@graygrids.com, we will immediately remove your email from the subscriber list.

 **Change of Privacy Policy:**  
This is the major change of our privacy policy and will be effective from 25th May 2018, If we make any more changes we will email you immediately.
